Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Congressmen profiles: Bill Wilson (36th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 19)
- Congressmen profiles: Van Deerlin (37th congressional district), 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 20)
- Congressmen profiles: Victor Veysey (38th congressional district), 1971 (Box 204, Folder 21)
- Carded names for Set the Date, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 22)
- Clergy and Laymen Concerned (Vietnam) names and addresses, undated (Box 204, Folder 23)
- Set the Date correspondence, 1972 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Set the Date future contracts, 1972 (Box 205, Folder 2)
- Bumper sticker file, 1972 (Box 205, Folder 3)
- Peace Action Council journal, pamphlets, and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 205, Folder 4)
- Peace Action Council summer and fall, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 5)
- Peace Action Council, 1967 January (Box 205, Folder 6)
- Peace Action Council mailing list, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 7)
- Pledge For Peace economic boycott, undated (Box 205, Folder 8)
- "Prime Time For the Opposition" by Professor Lewis M. Schwarts, 1967 June (Box 205, Folder 9)
- Peace Machines, Inc. brochure and correspondence, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 10)
- Anti-war groups: Committee directory and minutes, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 11)
- Anti-war groups: Peace organizations list, 1967-1969 (Box 205, Folder 12)
- Anti-war groups: Ad Hoc Committee membership list, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 13)
- Assembly of Men and Women in the Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 205, Folder 14)
- Campus tables and literature displayed, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 15)
- Clergy and Laymen Concerned (Vietnam) materials, 1968-1969 (Box 205, Folder 16)
- Computer Professionals for Peace, 1969 (Box 205, Folder 17)
- Committee on Critical Issues, 1965-1967 (Box 205, Folder 18)
- Dow Demonstrations report, 1968 (Box 205, Folder 19)
- Dow Chemical Senate meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 205, Folder 20)
- Dow Action Committee journals, pamphlet, and correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Zevin Proposal final form, 1967 (Box 206, Folder 2)
- Anti-draft events newspaper clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 206, Folder 3)
- Anti-draft groups: Anti-Complicity Movement newsletters, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 4)
- Anti-draft groups: Boston area group's dissent statement, 1968 January (Box 206, Folder 5)
- Anti-draft groups: Chicago Area Draft Resisters, 1967 (Box 206, Folder 6)
- Anti-draft groups: Chicago Area Draft Resisters, Gary Rader, and National Resistance Conference, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 7)
- Anti-draft groups: Campus draft oppositions, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 8)
- Civil Action Day Committee brochure, undated (Box 206, Folder 9)
- Committee for Draft Resistance, 1967-1968 (Box 206, Folder 10)
- Complicity and Benjamin Spock support statement, undated (Box 206, Folder 11)
- A Declaration of Conscience materials, 1967 (Box 206, Folder 12)
- Literature and correspondence on conscientious objectors, 1967 (Box 206, Folder 13)
- Literature, clippings, and correspondence on the draft, 1966-1967 (Box 207, Folder 1)
- Draft research, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 2)
- Draft Resistance League, Chomsky proposal and other materials, 1967 (Box 207, Folder 3)
- Draft Resistance Project national mobilization, 1967 (Box 207, Folder 4)
- Equal Time for CO in school and Board of Education, 1967 (Box 207, Folder 5)
- Freedom Draft Movement: "Guide to Conscientious Objection" by Levi Kingston, 1967-1968 (Box 207, Folder 6)
- Canada and immigration for war objectors clippings and handbook, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 7)
- Selective Service System, 1967 (Box 207, Folder 8)
- Draft boards correspondence, 1966 (Box 207, Folder 9)
- Stop the Draft Week list of those arrested, circa 1967 (Box 207, Folder 10)
- Political prisoners list and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 207, Folder 11)
- Marian Davis Scholarship Fund, 1969 May (Box 207, Folder 12)
- Mothers Against the Draft correspondence, 1967 May 13 (Box 207, Folder 13)
- Observer articles on draft resisters and correspondence, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 14)
- Organizations aiding conscientious objectors, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 15)
- Resist: Trial and post-conviction Paul Lauter, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 16)
- Resist: After indictments newsletter, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 17)
- Resist: Before indictments, 1967 (Box 207, Folder 18)
- Resist and support literature, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 19)
- THOI-BAO GA newsletter, 1971-1972 (Box 208, Folder 1)
- People's Coalition: Peace and Justice, Bradford Lyttle correspondence, and brochures, 1971-1973 (Box 208, Folder 2)
- Other literature, 1970-1971 (Box 208, Folder 3)
- May Tribe (Spring), 1971 (Box 208, Folder 4)
- Book lists, 1970-1971 (Box 208, Folder 5-6)
- Ephemera for anti-war silent vigil, 1966-1967 (Box 208, Folder 7)
- Vietnam newsletters and correspondence (Summer), 1967 (Box 208, Folder 8)
- Women Strike for Peace, 1967-1970 (Box 209, Folder 1-2)
- War Crimes Tribunal clippings, journal, and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 209, Folder 3)
- Western Penn. Academic Council newsletter, 1967 (Box 209, Folder 4)
- West Side Committee of Concern, 1967-1969 (Box 209, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and clippings for "Women For", 1967 (Box 209, Folder 6)
- Off-campus and other campus vigils, 1966-1968 (Box 209, Folder 7)
- Women Strike For Peace newsletter and journal, 1970-1973 (Box 209, Folder 8)
- Peace Child Foundation and Concerned Faculty correspondence, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 9)
- Emergency Black Survival Fund, 1983 (Box 210, Folder 1)
- Chomsky early materials, 1973-1983 (Box 210, Folder 2-3)
- Other Chomsky materials, 1982 (Box 210, Folder 4)
- Alliance for Survival Los Angeles, 1981-1983 (Box 210, Folder 5)
- Common Cause correspondence and newsletter, 1981 (Box 210, Folder 6)
- Joint sponsorship, 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 7)
- Concerned Faculty correspondence, 1982 (Box 210, Folder 8)
- Physicians for Social Responsibility educational materials, 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 9)
- Feminist Press Abortion Fund, 1979-1983 (Box 210, Folder 10)
- National Interreligious Service Board for Conscientious Objectors and veterans safe return, 1973-1982 (Box 211, Folder 1)
- Mailing labels, circa 1978 (Box 211, Folder 2)
- Concerned Faculty mailing list, 1982 August (Box 211, Folder 3)
- Middle East Peace Group and Lebanon mailing list, undated (Box 211, Folder 4)
- Concerned Faculty materials, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 5-11)
- Rape prevention material and Almut Poole, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 12)
- Freeze initiative clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 13)
- Owen Chamberlain's correspondence, undated (Box 211, Folder 14)
- Freeze initiative, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 15)
- Southern Poverty Law Center, 1983 February 17 (Box 211, Folder 16)
- Materials on other movements, 1980-1983 (Box 211, Folder 17-18)
- Center for Constitutional Rights, 1983 May 3 (Box 212, Folder 1)
- Amnesty International, 1983 (Box 212, Folder 2)
- Legal defense organizations, 1980-1983 (Box 212, Folder 3)
- Council for a Livable World, 1982 (Box 212, Folder 4)
- Sane World newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 212, Folder 5)
- Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1980-1983 (Box 212, Folder 6)
- Issue of The Nation, 1981 August 22-29 (Box 212, Folder 7)
- American Friends Service Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 212, Folder 8)
- American Civil Liberties Union correspondence, 1982 (Box 212, Folder 9)
- Middle East Peace projects, circa 1980 (Box 212, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Tony Martin's notes, undated (Box 213, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Tests and answer key, 1957-1970 (Box 213, Folder 2-5)
- Philosophy 133: Records (Spring), 1977 (Box 213, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 133: Final exam (Fall), 1974 (Box 213, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 133: Working materials (Fall), 1974-1976 (Box 213, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 133: Records (Spring), 1980 (Box 213, Folder 9)
- Metamathematics, 1965 March 31 (Box 213, Folder 10)
- Metamathematics, 1965 March 17, 24 (Box 213, Folder 11)
- Metamathematics (Spring), 1965 (Box 213, Folder 12)
- Syntactical development of Dana's metatheorem, David Kaplan, undated (Box 213, Folder 13)
- David's notes on modal logic and correspondence, 1965 (Box 213, Folder 14)
- David's logic of non-denoting terms and empty domains, 1965 (Box 213, Folder 15)
- Charles Howard semantics notes, undated (Box 213, Folder 16)
- Dana's modal logic correspondence, 1965 January 28 (Box 213, Folder 17)
- "Modal Logic Quantification Theory" by Dana Scott, 1965 August 1 (Box 213, Folder 18)
- Validity II modalities, undated (Box 213, Folder 19)
- Modalities notes, undated (Box 213, Folder 20)
- Krieke's lecture on model theory and notes, undated (Box 213, Folder 21)
- Modal logic and Independence Mapes, undated (Box 213, Folder 22)
- Notes for talk on modal logic semantical explored, 1959 (Box 214, Folder 1)
- Nino Cocchiarella paper, 1968 (Box 214, Folder 2)
- "Principles of Logic," Montague and Kalish, circa 1959 (Box 214, Folder 3)
- Modal logic notes, undated (Box 214, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Exams (Spring), 1975 (Box 214, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Notes (Fall), 1977 (Box 214, Folder 6)
- Wade Savage rebuttal to Reddin editorial, 1969 December (Box 214, Folder 7)
- Cohen photograph, circa 1984 (Box 214, Folder 8)
- "The Non-Correction Method and the Delayed Response Problem of Blodgett and McCutchan", 1946 April (Box 214, Folder 9)
- Blodgett paper data: Blodgett's method and six trials, circa 1945 (Box 214, Folder 10)
- Blodgett paper data: Non-correction method, circa 1945 (Box 214, Folder 11)
- Blodgett paper: Contiguity experiment, circa 1945 (Box 214, Folder 12)
- Angela Davis clippings and articles, 1969-1995 (Box 214, Folder 13)
- Angela Davis newspaper clippings, circa 1969 (Box 215, Folder 1-2)
- Amsterdam appeal, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Notes (Fall), 1971 (Box 215, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 133: Records (Winter), 1972 (Box 215, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 133 materials, 1974 (Box 215, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 133: Notes (Winter), 1972 (Box 215, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 133: Notes on set theory, 1972 (Box 215, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 133: Lectures and syllabus (Spring), 1977 (Box 215, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 133: Lectures, syllabus, and bibliography (Fall), 1975 (Box 216, Folder 1-2)
- Philosophy 133: Records, final exams, and other exams (Fall), 1985 (Box 216, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 133: Exercises (Winter), 1984 (Box 216, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 133: Current materials (Spring), 1989 (Box 216, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 133: Lectures (Fall), 1974 (Box 216, Folder 6-7)
- Files labelled "Volume I", 1966-1988 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  Labels include Committee on Internal Security, military records, "an attempt to get ride of Davis and Kalish," and "Post Dispatch, student paper."
- Files labelled "Volume II", 1954-1994 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  Topics include anti-Nixon rally, Watergate subpoena's, correspondence with Charles Berger over briefcase lost at Nixon rally, and Concerned Faculty.
- Photograph of fraternity, circa 1941 (Box 217, Folder 3)
- Personal correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 217, Folder 4)
- Anti-war teach-in and protest, 1965-1966 (Box 217, Folder 5)
- Personal correspondence, 1937-1972 (Box 217, Folder 6)
- Personal correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 217, Folder 7)
- Track team photographs, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 1)
- Photograph of car with bumper stickers, undated (Box 218, Folder 2)
- Rugby team newspaper clipping, 1941 May 11 (Box 218, Folder 3)
- Childhood and personal photographs, undated (Box 218, Folder 4)
- Correspondence related to Kalish's death, 2000 (Box 218, Folder 5)
- Personal correspondence, 1927-1940 (Box 218, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 218, Folder 7)
- Dream notes, 1966-1978 (Box 218, Folder 8)
- Organic Act 1868, 1969 (Box 220, Folder 1)
- Daily Bruin coverage of Angela Davis, 1969-1970 (Box 220, Folder 2)
- The Lincoln Star, 1969 October 22 (Box 220, Folder 3)
- Angela Davis CPUSA, undated (Box 220, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings on Angela Davis, 1969-1972 (Box 220, Folder 5)
- Anti-Kalish editorials and replies, 1969-1970 (Box 220, Folder 6)
- SM Evening Outlook coverage of Angela Davis, 1969 September (Box 220, Folder 7)
- Material on Angela Davis, 1969 (Box 220, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Times Angela Davis coverage, 1969-1972 (Box 220, Folder 9)
- Common Cause newspaper clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 220, Folder 10)
- Inter-University Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 220, Folder 11)
- Grass Roots, People's Action Union, 1975 (Box 220, Folder 12)
- Bridge the Gap, 1974-1979 (Box 220, Folder 13)
- Free India, undated (Box 220, Folder 14)
- Newspaper clippings on Angela Davis, 1969 (Box 221, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings on Angela Davis, 1970-1971 (Box 221, Folder 2)
- Communists, Divale article and sequel, 1969 July (Box 221, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams (Spring), 1966 (Box 221, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Spring), 1964 (Box 221, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31 (Spring), 1969 (Box 221, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Exams, undated (Box 221, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 30: Final exams, 1950-1956 (Box 221, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 102: Second exam, 1962 November (Box 221, Folder 9)
- Bibliographical materials, 1959-1966 (Box 221, Folder 10)
- Public Speaking 1A and 107AB syllabus, 1945 March (Box 222, Folder 1)
- "Introduction to Modern Logic", 1963 (Box 222, Folder 2)
- Book of Philosophy, undated (Box 222, Folder 3)
- The Military, 1961-1971 (Box 222, Folder 4)
- "On ABM and Other Military Foolishness", 1967-1970 (Box 222, Folder 5)
- Anti-ABM and MIT, 1967-1969 (Box 222, Folder 6)
- "The Power of the Pentagon" magazine article, 1969 June (Box 222, Folder 7)
- American militarism article in Look, 1969 August 12 (Box 222, Folder 8)
- Congressional Conference on the Military Budget and National Priorities report, 1969 June 2 (Box 222, Folder 9)
- Bay of Pigs, Columbia University Forum (Fall), 1967 (Box 222, Folder 10)
- Chicago Conspiracy Trial, 1970 March 23 (Box 223, Folder 1)
- Leaflets, calls, and announcements, 1968-1971 (Box 223, Folder 2)
- "Why Dissent Turns Violent" by Kingsley Widmer in The Nation, 1969 April 7 (Box 223, Folder 3)
- NUC crisis paper, undated (Box 223, Folder 4)
- The Nine for Peace photographs, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 5)
- "On Civil Disobedience," R. McAfee Brown's statement, 1968 November 18 (Box 223, Folder 6)
- "On The Resistance," Ferber and Harris, 1967-1968 (Box 223, Folder 7)
- "The Elementary Theory of Classes", undated (Box 223, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 31: Course evaluations (Summer), 1969 (Box 223, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 31: Quizzes and grades (Summer), 1969 (Box 223, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 31 (Summer), 1969 (Box 223, Folder 11)
- Logic appreciation, undated (Box 223, Folder 12)
- Draft of "Introduction to Modern Logic", undated (Box 223, Folder 13)
- "Resist", 1977-1979 (Box 223, Folder 14)
- "Resist", 1973-1977 (Box 224, Folder 1)
- Amnesty International, 1973-1977 (Box 224, Folder 2)
- Teach-in on repression newspaper clippings, 1969 (Box 224, Folder 3)
- Cleveland Peace Meeting (Summer), 1969 (Box 224, Folder 4)
- The New Democratic Coalition, undated (Box 224, Folder 5)
- IRS and court documents, 1967-1970 (Box 224, Folder 6)
- President's Commission on Violence, 1969 January (Box 225, Folder 1)
- Civil Disturbance Manual, 1967-1976 (Box 225, Folder 2)
- Newton-Cleaver Rally and Defense Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 225, Folder 3)
- Mrs. Francis E. Eisenberg material on Spock trial, 1968-1969 (Box 225, Folder 4)
- Sid Lens, Fort Hood Three (ASUCLA) programs, 1968-1969 (Box 225, Folder 5)
- California Democratic Council, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 6)
- Leonard M. Henny, 1968-1969 (Box 225, Folder 7)
- Committee for a New University clippings, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 8)
- Peace Action Council, 1968-1969 (Box 225, Folder 9)
- Japan Congress against atomic and hydrogen bombs, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 10)
- American Committee for Solidarity with the Vietnamese People, 1969 September (Box 225, Folder 11)
- "Congressmen: Communications and Statements" clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 225, Folder 12)
- Complaint in suit for refund of federal excise taxes, Altman, 1968-1969 (Box 225, Folder 13)
- Letters to IRS and other agencies from Tax Refusers, undated (Box 225, Folder 14)
- Tax refusal, Kalish correspondence, and clippings, 1968 (Box 226, Folder 1)
- "Illegality of War", 1968-1970 (Box 226, Folder 2)
- Southern California Tax Payers Against the War, 1970 (Box 226, Folder 3)
- Taxpayers Against the War, 1967 (Box 226, Folder 4)
- Tax protest, 1967 (Box 226, Folder 5)
- Telephone tax suit newspaper clipping, 1969 October 15 (Box 226, Folder 6)
- Evaluation of Hubert Humphrey, 1968 September 6 (Box 226, Folder 7)
- Demonstration fliers, undated (Box 226, Folder 8)
- Tax protest newspaper clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 226, Folder 9)
- George E. Brown, 1965-1970 (Box 226, Folder 10)
- Evelyn and Erik Whitehorn, 1969 May 6 (Box 226, Folder 11)
- Center for Constitutional Rights, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 12)
- Humphrey/McCarthy records on foreign policy, SANE, 1968 July (Box 227, Folder 1)
- "Documentary Interlock", undated (Box 227, Folder 2)
- Berkeley Defense Committee, 1969 (Box 227, Folder 3)
- Electors to vote for McCarthy, 1968 (Box 227, Folder 4)
- New York Review presentations, 1969-1970 (Box 227, Folder 5)
- National Service Board for Religious Objectors, 1969 February (Box 227, Folder 6)
- Fund for Education in World Order, 1969 March 5 (Box 227, Folder 7)
- The Institute for the Study of Nonviolence, 1969-1970 (Box 227, Folder 8)
- Anti-war materials, 1969-1970 (Box 227, Folder 9)
- Chicago 15, 1969 September (Box 227, Folder 10)
- "Lessons of '67" article, 1977 October (Box 227, Folder 11)
- People's Lobby, 1969 (Box 227, Folder 12)
- June 23 declaration and statements, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 13)
- LAPD handling of demonstrations, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 14)
- Putnam editorials, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 15)
- PAC statement for commission hearing, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 16)
- Kalish's statement on Century City, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 17)
- Century City injunction, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 18)
- Declarations on Century City (Sharon Stewart, Gray Hines, C.C. Lawyer), 1967 (Box 227, Folder 19)
- Regina Nadelson correspondence, 1972 January 12 (Box 227, Folder 20)
- "In the army", 1941-1942 (Box 228, Folder 1)
- Student projects, 1971 (Box 228, Folder 2)
- California Department of Corrections, 1970 (Box 228, Folder 3)
- Soledad and San Quentin newspaper clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 228, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 228, Folder 5)
- Playboy magazine, 1971 February (Box 228, Folder 6)
- "Poor People in Jail," Rodney L. Patterson, 1971 (Box 228, Folder 7)
- Joanne Perler and David S. Rubin on prisons, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 1)
- "The Man," Michael A. Giannelli, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 2)
- "Repression of the Police," Tom Hazelleaf, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 3)
- "Structure and Tenure" (Cheri Derbyshire and Patrick Dooner), 1971 (Box 229, Folder 4)
- "Prisoners and Media" (Richard Felton, Steve McCrea, Gary Livingston, Cheryl McKinne), 1971 (Box 229, Folder 5)
- "Academic Freedom-Conduct" (Jeff Kaufman and Mark Gottlieb), 1971 (Box 229, Folder 6)
- "Racism and its International Implications," Lawrence Shelton, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 7)
- "Undercover Agents on Campus," Madeline Wenters, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 8)
- "Academic Freedom" (Richard Kaufman, Terry Rubin, Paul Baker), 1971 (Box 229, Folder 9)
- "Women in Prisons," Laura Kaplan, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 10)
- David Lees, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 11)
- Pat Parker, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 12)
- "Prisons: The Moral Issues," John Newton, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 13)
- Michael Abzug, undated (Box 229, Folder 14)
- Jon A. Sigurdsson, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 15)
- Corinne Marin, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 16)
- "Regental Authority/Davis," Dean Ricker, 1971 (Box 229, Folder 17)
- "Los Angeles Community Colleges," Virginia Bunin, 1970 February (Box 229, Folder 18)
- "Environment" (Craig H. Hentschel, Alan Mirman, Rick Plaskoff), 1971 February (Box 229, Folder 19)
- Kathleen Longley exam and project, 1971 March (Box 229, Folder 20)